<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="opensource_multilingual_application">ইউটিউব মিউজিক থেকে গান স্ট্রিম করার একটা অপেনসোর্স বহুভাষার এন্ড্রোয়েড এপ্লিকেশন</string>
    <string name="your_library">আপনার লাইব্রেরি</string>
    <string name="organized_in_one_place">সব এক জায়গায় গোছানো, আপনার প্রিয় গান, ডাওনলোড করা গান, শোনা গান আর আপনার সব প্লে লিস্টও।</string>
    <string name="beautiful_player">একটা সুন্দর প্লেয়ার</string>
    <string name="listen_songs_sing_lyrics">গান শুনুন, লিরিকের সাথে গান, বিল্ট ইন ট্রান্সলেটর দিয়ে লিরিক অনুবাদ করুন</string>
    <string name="many_effects">অনেক ইফেক্ট</string>
    <string name="visualizer_preview_timeline">ভিজুয়ালাইজার, প্রিভিউ, টাইমলাইন, প্লে বাটন, আপনার ইচ্ছামত ইফেক্ট এপ্লাই করুন।</string>
    <string name="modern">আধুনিক</string>
    <string name="rimusic_is_multilingual_modern_powerful"> N-Zik বহু ভাষায়, আধুনিক, শক্তিশালী, আকর্ষণীয়, সুন্দর গান শোনার এপ্লিকেশন এবং প্রজেক্ট কোলাবরেটরদের মাধ্যমে বহুভাষায় অনুদিত হয়েছে। </string>
    <string name="listen_to_your_favourite_music">আপনার প্রিয় গান শুনুন</string>
    <string name="download_rimusic_now">এখনো N-Zik ডাওনলোড করুন</string>
    <string name="repository">রিপোজিটরি</string>
    <string name="releases">রিলিজ</string>
    <string name="issue_tracker">ইস্যু ট্র‍্যকার</string>
    <string name="custom_version">কাস্টম ভার্শন</string>
    <string name="feat_modern_ui">Modern &amp; Intuitive UI.</string>
    <string name="feat_modern_ui_desc">Enjoy a refined user experience with a beautiful interface, seamless navigation, and YouTube integration.</string>
    <string name="feat_lyrics">Advanced Lyrics Support.</string>
    <string name="feat_lyrics_desc">Fetch, display, edit, and translate lyrics in real-time with precise word-by-word synchronization.</string>
    <string name="feat_visualizer">Immersive Audio Visualizer.</string>
    <string name="feat_visualizer_desc">Enjoy real-time visual effects synchronized perfectly with your music.</string>
    <string name="feat_discord">Discord Rich Presence.</string>
    <string name="feat_discord_desc">Show off your current musical vibe by displaying your playing track directly on your Discord profile.</string>
    <string name="feat_stats">Listening Statistics.</string>
    <string name="feat_stats_desc">Track your listening habits, favorite artists, and playback trends over time.</string>
    <string name="feat_caching">Smart Offline Caching.</string>
    <string name="feat_caching_desc">Automatically cache songs for offline playback with customizable limits, or download tracks for permanent access.</string>
    <string name="feat_search">Search &amp; Voice Search.</string>
    <string name="feat_search_desc">Easily find your favorite tracks, albums, and artists, even with your voice.</string>
    <string name="feat_ota">OTA Updates.</string>
    <string name="feat_ota_desc">Receive automatic in-app updates directly from GitHub without needing to manually download new APKs.</string>
    <string name="feat_carrousel">Carousel Player View.</string>
    <string name="feat_carrousel_desc">Enjoy a unique, visually stunning 3D carousel view for your music playback.</string>
    <string name="feat_artist">Detailed Artist Profiles.</string>
    <string name="feat_artist_desc">Explore comprehensive artist profiles with top tracks, albums, and similar artists.</string>
    <string name="feat_settings">Advanced Audio Controls.</string>
    <string name="feat_settings_desc">Customize your experience with advanced audio controls, backup/restore features, and more.</string>
    <string name="feat_voice">Hands-free Voice Search.</string>
    <string name="feat_voice_desc">Find music quickly without typing by using the built-in voice search functionality.</string>
    <string name="feat_playlists">Playlists Management.</string>
    <string name="feat_playlists_desc">Easily create, import, export, and manage your playlists in one unified interface.</string>
    <string name="feat_queue">Playback Queue.</string>
    <string name="feat_queue_desc">Keep track of what's playing next, rearrange songs on the fly, and manage your upcoming tracks.</string>
    <string name="feat_history">Complete History.</string>
    <string name="feat_history_desc">Never lose a song you loved. Access your complete listening history at any time.</string>
    <string name="feat_youtube">YouTube Integration.</string>
    <string name="feat_youtube_desc">Recommendations and profile-related content are synchronized directly from your YouTube account.</string>
    <string name="feat_presets">Theme Presets.</string>
    <string name="feat_presets_desc">Choose from 6 beautifully crafted visual themes to personalize your music experience.</string>
    <string name="feat_nav_compatibility">সামঞ্জস্য</string>
    <string name="feat_compatibility">একাধিক ডিভাইস সামঞ্জস্য।</string>
    <string name="feat_compatibility_desc">সর্বত্র আপনার সঙ্গীত উপভোগ করুন! N-Zik Android মোবাইল, Android Auto, Android Automotive এবং Android TV-এর সাথে সামঞ্জস্যপূর্ণ। (পরে Wear OS)।</string>
</resources>
